Guide to the Hunter Ripley Rawlings papers, 1995-2006.
Rawlings, Hunter Ripley papers, 1995-2006
- Series IV. Media
  - Committee on Alumni Affairs and Development Breakfast, Richard M. Ramin Tribute, October 13, 1995; V-984 (Box 105)
  - Convocation, March 7, 2003; V-985 (Box 105)
  - Commonwealth Club of California, Tape #1, October 11, 1991; V-986 (Box 105)
  - Cornell '51, The Class on the Cutting Edge, V-987 (Box 105)
  - Cornell "Awards", January 9, 1997; V-988 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Class of 1962 35th Reunion, June 5-8, 1997; V-989 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Campaign Video Version II, Without Rhodes, November 4, 1994; V-990 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Campaign (San Diego), V-991 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Campaign Volunteer Workout Trainer's Tape 2, V-992 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Emc2 Off-Line Edit, June 28, 1993; V-993 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Florida, 1995; V-994 (Box 105)
  - Cornell hockey team performing the Nutcracker on ice with Dick Button. This might actually be Swan Lake., October 26, 1992; V-995 (Box 105)
  - Cornell President Frank H. T. Rhodes Penn Halftime Spot, V-996 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Sports Network, September 26, 1992; V-997 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Sports Network Features, October 3, 1992; V-998 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Tradition: Portraits in Working, Sharing, and Learning, V-999 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Rough Cut #2, July 16, 1993; V-1000 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Rough Edit, July 13, 1993; V-1001 (Box 105)
  - Cornell Rough Edit, July 19, 1993; V-1002 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University Creating the Future 125th Anniversary, V-1003 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University Creating the Future Campaign, V-1004 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University Football 1991 Features, 1991; V-1005 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University Medical College Media Highlights, V-1006 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University President's Circle Dinner, January 22, 1997; V-1007 (Box 105)
  - Cornell University Scholarship Challenge Campaign, Campaign Launch Celebration, October 23, 1998; V-1008 (Box 105)
  - Cornell's Johnson School Capital Campaign, 1989; V-1009 (Box 105)
  - Dale Corson Cornell's Good Fortune, December 1999; V-1010 (Box 105)
  - The Late Show with David Letterman, this show was his first after having bypass surgery at Cornell Medical Center. The episode features many of the staff from Cornell Medical that were involved., February 21, 2000; V-1011 (Box 105)
  - Duffield Hall Dedication Ceremony, October 6, 2004; V-1012 (Box 105)
  - Gala Finale Celebration, October 11, 1991; V-1013 (Box 105)
  - Geographical Fugue, Cornell University Glee Club Concert Tour of Asia, 1989; V-1014 (Box 105)
  - "I Would Found..." Cornell University Promotional Spot (Student Version), May 17, 2004; V-1015 (Box 106)
  - Introduction of New President, luncheon, press conference, Jeffery Lehman, December 14, 2002; V-1016 (Box 106)
  - Cornell Campaign Volunteer Workout, Keys to Your Fund Raising Success, V-1017 (Box 106)
  - A Look Back, V-1018 (Box 106)
  - MacNeil / Lehrer Report, Susan Davenny-Wyner, V-1019 (Box 106)
  - Mike Borkowski, Heart One Racing, V-1020 (Box 106)
  - A New Horizon, V-1021 (Box 106)
  - National Education Goals Panel, April 13, 2000; V-1022 (Box 106)
  - Pacific Vision, Stanford Asia/Pacific Scholars Program, 1999; V-1023 (Box 106)
  - Super Class of '56 35th Reunion Invitation, 1991; V-1024 (Box 106)
  - Scholarship Luncheon, May 1, 1999; V-1025 (Box 106)
  - Snee Hall 10th Anniversary Message, V-1026 (Box 106)
  - 20/20 Sleep with James Maas, V-1027 (Box 106)
  - State of the University, Frank H. T. Rhodes, 1989; V-1028 (Box 106)
  - The Synthesis National Engineering Education Coalition, 1994; V-1029 (Box 106)
  - Television Coverage of Weill Gift. Sandy Weill, May 1998; V-1030 (Box 106)
  - The Cornell Campaign: Creating the Future, V-1031 (Box 106)
  - Cornell Victorious, January 24, 2002; V-1032 (Box 106)
  - The White House Conference on the Philanthropy Gifts of the Future, V-1033 (Box 106)
  - Weiss, Peck, & Greer 25th Anniversary, February 4, 1995; V-1034 (Box 106)
  - WebGenesis, CNN "It's Only Money", CNET "Hall of Fame", June 9, 1997; V-1035 (Box 106)
  - Yale University Facilities, November 19, 1997; V-1036 (Box 106)
  - McLamore Foundation Video Presentation. Burger King, Jim McLamore, October 31, 1996; V-1037 (Box 106)
  - Cornell/Sports Channel America Football Promo, 1992; V-1038 (Box 106)
  - Cornell University 125 Years of Creating the Future, James B. Maas Executive Producer, 8mm (Box 106)
  - A. D. White Reception, Convocation images, President Jeffery Lehman, President Bill Clinton, 2004; 297 (Box 106)
  - President Luncheon, images Frank H. T. Rhodes, 2004; 298 (Box 106)
  - Cornell Class of 1974 Call to 30th Reunion!, 2004; 299 (Box 106)
  - Cornell University Alumni Directory 2002, 2002; 300 (Box 106)
  - The Cornell Tradition Celebrating our 20th Anniversary, 2002; 197 (Box 106)